Oh oh, I think today
哦哦今天我想
Introduce azure machine learning to all your classmates
给各位同学来介绍一下azure机器学习
part of that if everyone
的一个部分那如果大家呢
Uh, have to watch the little video above and you'll know above
呃有看上面的小视频呢大家会知道azure上面
There are some very, uh, powerful machine learning
呢有非常呃强大的一些机器学习的
some features ah we uh before
一些功能啊啊我们呃之前
That introduces a zero code way to do it uh
呢就介绍过一个零代码的方式去做呃
A computer vision task then what follows I think
一个计算机视觉的任务那接下来呢我想
Give everyone a more professional part of everyone know what we do
给大家更专业的部分大家知道我们做
Machine learning will encounter a situation is er
机器学习的时候呢会遇到一个状况就是呃
We may not have gpu or some
我们可能没有gpu或者是没有一些
Machine learning platforms are also very much built in the environment
机器学习的平台还有搭建环境的时候非常
Inconvenient but if you get through the azure can be quick
不方便但是如果你通过azure了可以很快
Go quickly to get the job done you can't
速地去完成相关的工作你可以不
Need to pay attention to some of your entire uh platform
需要关注你的整个呃平台的一些
Build the situation ah installation ah profile and so on
搭建情况啊啊安装啊配置文件之类的
You can start some machine learning above your azure
就可以启动你的azure的一些机器学习上面的
Some services include saying logos include saying pythons
一些服务包括说logo包括说python的
The environment also has some gpu some calculation
环境还有就是一些gpu的一些算力的
Some uh use here words I would like to introduce to you
一些呃使用在这里面的话呢我想给大家介绍一下
Azure's whole uh machine learning one of the services
azure的整个呃机器学习的一个服务的一个
Platform good first of all we go back to azure portal
平台好首先呢我们回到azure的portal
There's going to be a lot of it in this slope
里面在这个坡头里面呢呃会有很多的
Some uh resources some create us too
一些呃资资源的一些创建我们呢
First of all, we're going to create an azure and about the machine
首先还是要去创建一个azure及关于机器
Service uh resources we go to choose ai
服务的呃资源我们去选择ai
Add machine learning and then define it here
加机器学习然后呢在这里面定义
Column uh inside uh the first one is us
列呃里面的呃第一个就是我们
The machine learning service then clicks To create that one
的机器学习服务然后点击创建那这个
Take him and you'll be guided to a machine learning
收了他就会引导你去做一个azure的一个机器学习
One of the creations here faces you can
的一个创建在这里面的话你可以
Choose the original resource group or yourself
选择的是原有的资源组或者是自己
You can create another one that you might want to create
可以新建一个另外的你可能是要去创建
A machine learning name er is like ldemo
一个机器学习的一个名字呃像ldemo
Oh then you
哦然后呢你
You can select your region then why your stored account should have
可以选择你的区域然后你的存储的账户为什么要有
Storage because, uh, it can help you if it's in there
存储呢因为呃在里面的话它可以帮你
To save your er Jubit's logo is also relevant
去保存你的呃朱比特的logo还有相关的
Some uh about the data sorting ah uh there's another
一些呃关于数据的整理啊呃还有另外的
Some related er includes talking about some of the exercises of training
一些相关的呃包括说训练的一些操作
And some uh keys
还有就是一些呃密钥啊啊
These are all very useful of course you need not go
这些都是一个非常有用的当然你需不需要去
Register a container ah can also default to not
注册一个容器了啊也可以默认可以不
Use ah here we don't need to start then
用啊在这里我们先不用然后就开始
Go and create that in the creation
去创建了那在创建
In the process he will go and do our verification
的过程当中他会去也是做我们的验证的
Step a little if
步骤稍等如果
If the validation passes then you can go directly to create when
验证通过的话你就可以直接的去创建了当
Anne's
安妮的
uh azuremachinelearning service up er
呃azuremachinelearning的服务了呃
Once it's been created, he'll tell you to go
已经创建了之后呢他就会可以告诉你去转到
Related resources inside that you can see
相关的资源里面那大家可以看
Get oh here if he has put the resources you need
得到哦在这里面的话他已经把你需要的资源
The group has been bound to the space that is of course also stored
组已经绑定了当然也在存储的空间
There are positions above that have made some bindings ah here
还有位置上面都做了一些绑定啊在这里
face you can go directly to use your azuremachine
面你就可以直接的去使用你的azuremachine
a platform for learning on this ah
learning的一个平台在这上面的话啊
We can click on it depending on the situation
我们可以根据呃情况呢去点击啊
Ah, the url in this studio
啊这个工作室里面的url啊
Go and jump to our azure machine service
去跳转到我们的azure机器服务
One uh related one connects that one
的一个呃相关的一个连接那这个
Then you can create love for you according to your needs
时候你就可以根据你的需要去创建爱你的
Uh, some public, uh, some related to machine learning
呃一些公呃跟机器学习相关的一些
Work example uh we may need to do machine learning
工作举个例子呃我们做机器学习可能需要
To logo then you this time you may be going to uh
到logo那你这个时候你可能是要去呃
Do the operation of logo ah here you can go
做logo的操作啊在这里面你可以去
Add ah new logo can also be uh
添加啊新的logo也可以呢呃
Go inside the sample because you're going to study then you can
去在sample里面因为你是要去学习那你可以在
Above go uh learn a uh add
上面去呃学习一个呃添加
How about a er-related one going
一个呃相关的一个怎么样子去
Use mlexperiment to operate that time
用mlexperiment的操作那这个时候呢
You can go to a folder in xsample
你可以去xsample的一个文件夹里面啊去
Clone it on top of your local like I'm in
把它克隆到你的本地上面像举个例子我在
Here is a catalogue of looking fees ah
这里是一个looking费的一个目录啊
It's my name and then clone him
是我的名字然后就克隆他就可以
Put the file inside uhsample uh clone the truth uh
把呃sample里面的文件呃克隆道理的呃
One directory above and then the words below it seem
一个目录上面然后呢在这下面的话好像
Said I was going to er mess up one of my sdka
说我要去呃乱我的一个sdka
ml sdk then I click on him
ml的sdk那我点击他的
file when you can find ah his ml
文件的时候大家可以发现啊他的ml
Ah, English is relatively tall but not afraid
啊都是英文比较高大上但是不怕
Ah, uh, all of them
啊啊在上面的话呢呃都是一些
How to go uh to take advantage of this
怎么样子去呃利用嗯这个
Azuremachinelearning does some model training
azuremachinelearning去做一些模型训练的
That's when people know you need to do something relevant
那这个时候大家知道你需要去做一些相关
some of the calculations uh then you this take
的一些算力呃那你这个收
He'll tell you what to do if you don't do the calculation
了他会告诉你你没有去做算力怎么办呢你要去
Choose a er new one
选择一个呃新的一个compute啊啊
Here you can choose is gpu and cpu
在这里面你可以选择的是gpu跟cpu
Thecomputer because I'm here for that
的computer因为我在这里的话啊是
Uh there's one you can use called m
呃有你可以用一个叫做m
When choosing gpu you can choose is er
选择gpu的时候你可以选择的是呃一个
m60 a gpu a calculation of course you
m六零的一个gpu的一个算力当然你
If it's a little saving, because you have students
如果是节省一点的话因为你有学生
Account ah has a hundred knives of a uh calculation
账号啊有一百刀的一个呃算力
A support for that time you can choose ah one
的一个支持那这个时候呢你可以选择啊一个
Gpu ah every hour to count 1.5
gpu啊啊每个小时来算就一点五
Eight dollars, 1.5558 knives
八美金啊一点五百五五八刀
Ah, a calculation ah so here in the words
啊啊的一个算力啊所以在这里面的话
Ah, you can do it according to your needs and this
啊你可以根据你的需要去做而且这个
It doesn't cost you to stop it when you don't use it
呢你不用的时候把它停掉它是不算任何费用
So you have to look at your own reality of course you
的所以呢你要看你自己的实际情况当然你
It can be used in the words of cpucpu it has a lot of cu
可以用cpucpu的话呢它有很多的cu
Uh--- the arithmetic is on it like I am here
的呃算力在上面像我在这里的话我就
Used a er plain called ds3v2
用了一个叫做ds三v二的一个呃普通
A cpu it is zero one four knives ah
的一个cpu它是零点一四刀啊
Uh four-and-a-half knives ah as every hour
呃四一刀啊啊作为每个小时
The calculation of which I create here is also false
的算力那我就在这里创建创建也是虚实
uh to create ah uh it
呃去创建啊呃它
Will create a success will tell you oh this thing is how
会创建成功之后就会告诉你哦这个东西是怎么样
Son of the uh you can see ha
子的嗯大家可以看得到哈
Oh, and you don't need to put in your calculations
哦你的算力也不需要去投入啊
Itch and you can go uh do a lot
痒而且呢你可以去呃做很多
Some machine learning-related work is else here
的一些机器学习相关的工作另外呢在这里
Face I would like to introduce to you a very interesting
面我想介绍给大家一个非常好玩的
The thing is his game and we're waiting to calculate
东西就是他的比赛呢我们在等待计算
Well, this calculation er-creative start-up
嗯的这个算力呃创启动
You can go to the game when you get up
起来的时候呢你就可以去看一下这个比赛了
What is this third?
这个第三呢是什么东西呢大家知道在
Windows above well we can be very simple
windows上面嗯我们可以很简单的
Go drag and drop some controls to complete some windows
去拖拽一些控件去完成一些windows
The interface ah here in the words you can
的界面啊在这里面的话呢你可以
Through ah related uh one
通过啊相关的呃一个
uh drag uh to finish machine learning inside related
呃拖拽呃去完成机器学习里面相关
Some knowledge of some creation as I am here for everyone
的一些知识的一些创建像我在这里的话大家
You can see that I have selected an image recognition action
可以看到我我选择了一个图像识别的操作
And then, uh, if you choose this game you can watch
之后呢呃如果你选择这个比赛呢你可以看
to it from the graphic image hurry ah to the image
到它从图图像急啊到图像的
Some transition to some categories of image pictures
一些转变到图像图片的一些分类哎到
Training is done by dragging
训练都是通过拖拽去完成的这样子
Then he'll make machine learning even more uh
的话呢他就让机器学习更加的呃
Automation is so good
自动化啊可是话啊啊所以
Well, uh through azure machine learning service you can uh through
呢呃通过azure的机器学习服务了你可以呃通过
Designer to complete the steps of your machine learning
设计器去完成你的机器学习的步骤
It is also another popular use in the industry
另外的也还可以用业界最受欢迎
automl to complete related tasks
的automl去完成相关的任务
It is also very convenient to use then we go back
也是非常方便可用的然后我们回到
Our logo to see if he's finished
我们的logo去看一下他是不是已经创建完了
Good when we calculate
好当我们的算
After the force is created ah you can see that he will go
力创建完之后啊大家可以看得到他会去
Remind you oh this calculation has been created successfully then
提醒你哦这个算力已经创建成功了然后
At this time, uh, people will be worried
在这个时候呢呃大家会担心的是
Alas, my calculation is to use the three environment to give you an example
哎呀我这个算力究竟是用三者环境举个例子你
You can use python 3.6
可以用的是python三点六的
Of course, the environment can also use 3.8 ah and there is another
环境当然也可以用三点八啊还有另外的
It also supports r as a support for this calculation force so
它也支持r的这种算力的一个支持所以
It's very convenient to be here
呢在这里面呢是非常方便的啊而且
You can go online through uhlogo
你可以通过呃logo的去线上的
This logo goes to add code and then runs so
这个logo呢去添加代码然后运行所以呢
Services via auremachinelearning, uh
通过azuremachinelearning的服务呢呃
can let your machine learn er uh learn
可以让你的机器学习了呃呃学习
Or the experimental environment gets a boost and
或者实验的环境呢得到一个提升而且
It's going to be done without paying
是在呃不用付费的前提下去
Finish this thing ah hope that all the students ah immediately
完成这个事啊希望各位同学了啊马上
Go and try it, uh, through the azure
去尝试一下啊呃通过azure的
Machine learning services to complete your uhai
机器学习服务去完成你的呃ai的
Learning ah can also be used as a learning environment ah
学习啊也可以作为学习的环境啊
Thank you
谢谢大家